你都不在乎
And you don't care.
不不  我要组建一支队伍
No, no. I'm putting together the team.
绿巨人是火
The Hulk is the fire.
等等  你是在利用我得到绿巨人
Wait, you're just using me to get to the Hulk.
-什么  -真过分
- What? - It's gross.
什么  不是的
What? No!
你才不在乎我呢  你不是我的朋友
You don't care about me. You're not my friend.
才不是  我都不喜欢绿巨人  他就...
No! I don't even like the Hulk. He's all like...
"砸扁  砸扁  砸扁"
"Smash, smash, smash."
我更喜欢你
I prefer you.
谢谢
Thanks.
但老实说  在对抗邪恶化身这件事上
But if I'm being honest, when it comes to fighting evil beings,
他是很强大很有帮助
he is very powerful and useful.
班纳也很强大很有帮助
Yeah, Banner's powerful and useful, too.
是吗
Is he though?
好吧  绿巨人有几个博士学位  零
Okay. How many PhDs does Hulk have? Zero.
班纳有多少个博士学位  七个
How many PhDs does Banner have? Seven.